<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Everything iPhone, iPad And Android News and Tutorials | Telephony Lebanon</title>
    <description>Telephony a weblog dedicated on delivering mobile phone latest news, how to fix, information guides and tutorials about the iPhone, iPad and Android.</description>
    <link>http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 10:35:45 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 10:35:45 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Google posts Q4 and full year 2015 earnings – $74.5 billion in revenue for the year</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alphabet has just posted Google’s Q4 and full year 2015 financial results, showing massive growth for the company year over year, as well as a big jump in revenue in Q4 alone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we get into the details, we should clarify a few things. Now that Google has a parent company, things are going to be a bit different when it comes to financial results. Alphabet has separated its core businesses – Search, Maps, YouTube, Apps, Cloud, Ads, Commerce, Android, Chrome, Google Play and hardware sales – from its more farfetched endeavors, or “Other Bets.”. Alphabet’s core businesses are still referred to as Google, the company we all know and love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we have all of that cleared up, let’s get into some numbers. Taking a look at Google’s revenues alone, the company has posted a full year revenue of $74.5 billion, up 13 percent year-over-year, as well as a total of $23.42 billion in profit for the full year. The company has earned $21.33 billion in revenue in Q4 2015, up 18 percent year-over-year, with a Q4 net income of $4.9 billion, up from $4.6 billion at the same time last year. Those are the important numbers when it comes to Google’s businesses, so let’s move on to the Other Bets.
Alphabet’s Other Bets consist of other projects such as Google Fiber, Nest, Calico, GV (Google Ventures), Google Capital, X (Google X) and a few other important initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For all of 2015, the company’s Other Bets earned a total of $448 million in revenue, up from $327 million year-over-year. These numbers aren’t all that high, especially when considering the Other Bets operating loss of $3.57 billion for the full year. Of course, these are largely experimental projects, so it shouldn’t really be a surprise that these businesses didn’t make the company any money.
For more financial details, follow the source link below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://abc.xyz/investor/&quot;&gt;Google Offical Earnings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/google-earnings</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/google-earnings</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tech</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple said to unveil new 4-inch iPhone 5se, iPad Air 3 and new Apple Watch bands on March 15</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Apple is currently aiming to unveil the new 4-inch the iPhone 5se, the iPad Air 3, and new Apple Watch band options at an event on Tuesday, March 15th, according to sources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We previously reported that Apple was on track to launch the new products during the week of March 14th. As the scheduled event is still a month-and-a-half away, the date could conceivably still shift or turn into an online announcement. The media event would be Apple’s first since September, and much like the fall event, is planned to touch on three major product categories for the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;iphone-5se&quot;&gt;iPhone 5se&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/iPhone-5se-leak.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;iPhone 5se leak&quot; title=&quot;iPhone 5se vs iPhone 5&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Claimed iPhone 5se, at right, versus the iPhone 5, at left.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the rumors are accurate, the iPhone 5se should give customers who prefer smaller form factors something to be excited about. The handset will have a four-inch screen like the iPhone 5s, but run Apple’s in-house designed 64-bit A9 chip, plus NFC for Apple Pay, enhanced cameras and Live Photos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ipad-air-3-cover&quot;&gt;iPad Air 3 Cover&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/iPad-Air-3-case-leak.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Apple iPad Air 3&quot; title=&quot;iPad Air 3 case&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;First iPad Air 3 case out of China.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the iPad Air 3, claimed design drawings suggest the 9.7-inch tablet refresh boasts four speakers and the Smart Connector like the iPad Pro. It could also support the Apple Pencil and have a LED flash on the back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;apple-new-band-watch&quot;&gt;Apple New Band Watch&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/new-Apple-Watch.png&quot; alt=&quot;Apple New band Watch&quot; title=&quot;New Apple Watch band&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The new band lines will include multiple new colors for the rubberized Sport Bands, new Hermes bands, a Space Black version of the Milanese Loop, and an entirely new band line made of a new material&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;http://9to5mac.com/2016/02/02/march-15-event-4-inch-phone-new-ipad-apple-watch/&quot;&gt;9To5Mac&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/apple-leaked-iphone-5se</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/apple-leaked-iphone-5se</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tech</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple Music for Android update adds save to SD card for offline listening</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Apple released an update for the Apple Music app on the Android platform via the Google Play Store on Wednesday with a much-needed new feature: the ability to save songs from the app to your Android device’s removable SD card storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What’s New&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;This update adds downloading songs to an SD card, so you can now keep more music offline. You can also:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;See the full schedule of Beats 1 shows, making it easy to tune into your favorite ones.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Browse My Music by Composers, and Compilations, which help you find music your classical albums or movie soundtracks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The update makes it easier for Android users to use the Beats 1 radio station by making it possible to see a full schedule of shows and improving the experience of trying to find your favorite ones to follow, and it even makes it possible to perform searches for composers or compilations, which will make finding certain kinds of music a lot easier on specific users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Music is still very much in beta on the Android platform, but it works entirely the same as the iOS counterpart, allowing users to stream music off of Apple’s online catalogs for a monthly price of $9.99. Android users also get the same 3-month free trial option that Apple users have, which is a plus for anyone wanting to try it out before they buy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple Music for Android is a &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.apple.android.music&amp;amp;hl=en&quot;&gt;free download&lt;/a&gt; from the Google Play Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have an Android device, will you be grabbing today’s Apple Music update? Share in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/apple-music-update-android</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://telephony-lebanon.github.io/apple-music-update-android</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tech</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
